{
  "sections": [
    {
      "title": "Rules",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "Rules",
          "question": "Rules",
          "answer": "1. Drink 3/4 glasses of water or water with syrup or juice !    \n2. Max 1 coffe, 1 tea, 1 milk daily !    \n---\n3. No more screen time that 2hrs, other than coding or tutorials !  \n---\n4. Start coding by 7 !  \n5. Code for 4 hrs daily !  \n6. Tutorials for 1hr daily !  \n---\n7. No coding past 18:00 !  \n8. No computers past 20:00 !  \n9. No mobile phone past 22:00 !\n---\n10. Sleep 8 hrs, from 23:00 most late !  \n---\n11. Exercice daily !  \n12. Walk at least weekly !  \n---  \nPut pass/fail daily for these points. \n",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T19:17:34.799Z"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Log",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "19.12.2023",
          "question": "19.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. pass\n2. fail \n---\n3. fail\n---\n4. fail  \n5. pass  \n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail  \n---\n11. fail  \n12. fail",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T19:18:32.677Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "20.12.2023",
          "question": "20.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. pass  \n2. pass  \n---\n3. fail, to time it\n---\n4. fail, 11:30    \n5. pass  \n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail, 1-9\n---\n11. fail  \n12. fail",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T19:18:41.088Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "21.12.2023",
          "question": "21.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. fail\n2. pass  \n---\n3. fail, to time it\n---\n4. fail    \n5. pass  \n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail, 1-9\n---\n11. fail  \n12. fail",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T19:18:48.080Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "22.12.2023",
          "question": "22.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. pass  \n2. pass  \n---\n3. fail, to time it\n---\n4. fail    \n5. pass  \n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail, 1-9\n---\n11. fail  \n12. fail",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T19:19:44.558Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "23.12.2023",
          "question": "23.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. pass  \n2. pass  \n---\n3. fail, to time it\n---\n4. fail    \n5. fail, 1,5\n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail, 1-9\n---\n11. fail  \n12. fail",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T19:19:53.334Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "24.12.2023",
          "question": "24.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. fail \n2. pass   \n---\n3. fail\n---\n4. fail  \n5. fail, 2,5\n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail  \n---\n11. fail  \n12. fail",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T19:20:02.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "25.12.2023",
          "question": "25.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. fail  \n2. pass   \n---\n3. fail, to time\n---\n4. fail  \n5. pass, 8 pomodoro\n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail  \n---\n11. fail\n12. pass (walk with dad, his neighborhood)",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-25T23:22:19.097Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "26.12.2023",
          "question": "26.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. fail  \n2. pass  \n---\n3. fail, to time  \n---\n4. fail  \n5. fail  , 5 pomodoro\n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail  \n---\n11. fail\n12. fail  ",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-27T14:42:04.955Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "27.12.2023",
          "question": "27.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. fail  \n2. fail  \n---\n3. fail, to time  \n---\n4. fail  \n5. pass, 9 pomodoro\n6. fail  \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail  \n---\n11. fail\n12. fail  ",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-27T22:01:38.535Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "28.12.2023",
          "question": "28.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. pass  \n2. fail, 2 coffe    \n---\n3. fail, to time  \n---\n4. fail  \n5. pass, 8 pomodoro\n6. fail, 1 pomodoro   \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail  \n---\n11. fail\n12. fail  ",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-28T21:33:48.240Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "29.12.2023",
          "question": "29.12.2023",
          "answer": "1. fail  \n2. pass    \n---\n3. fail, to time  \n---\n4. fail  \n5. fail, 6 pomodoro\n6. fail   \n---\n7. fail\n8. fail  \n9. fail\n---  \n10. fail  \n---\n11. fail\n12. pass, grocery shoping in biedronka 3 siatki  ",
          "dateTime": "2023-12-29T22:53:54.258Z"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}